<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>XPhyro&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://xphyro.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on XPhyro&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC-SA 4.0&lt;/a&gt; &amp; &lt;a href=&#34;https://opensource.org/licenses/MIT&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;MIT&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 21:06:25 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xphyro.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Lost Ark - A Review</title>
      <link>https://xphyro.github.io/articles/2022/02/19/lost-ark-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 21:06:25 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xphyro.github.io/articles/2022/02/19/lost-ark-review/</guid>
      <description>This game has an abundance of deal-breakers:
Queue times are so large that the game sometimes does not even let you get in queue. When it lets you, expect 6 hours or more. Booting up takes minutes. Opening most UI elements in-game freezes the game for a few seconds. Time-gated end-game: limited chaos dungeons, scheduled raids, timed stronghold upgrades and more. Uninspired, unchallenging and boring progression until the beginning of the end-game (level 50-ish).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up A Personal Blog</title>
      <link>https://xphyro.github.io/articles/2021/07/15/setting-up-a-personal-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 09:09:28 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xphyro.github.io/articles/2021/07/15/setting-up-a-personal-blog/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, I will explain the steps for creating a blog like mine: static, automatically generated and hosted for free.
Framework I have built this blog using Hugo and the hello-friend-ng theme, and host it on GitHub Pages.
Workflow I use a private Git repository to version the development side of the blog (such that drafts will not be public), and use a public repository named xphyro.github.io to host the public web site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://xphyro.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 22:39:40 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xphyro.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Me Education I am currently a fourth-year undergraduate in the physics department of Middle East Technical University. I like mathematics, physics and computer science. So far, my undergraduate research mainly revolve around computational physics.
General Interests Below are my current non-academic interests along with when I got into them.
Interest Year-Quadrant Programming 2012-? Game Development 2014-? Archery 2015-2 Mountain Biking 2017-2 Classical Guitar 2018-3 Piano 2021-3 Blog Topic I write about all sorts of stuff and in various forms.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
